I gave my knife to the static, gave my breath to the flood, let the room fill up with shadows while I tried to call
about him pulling the gun again and like threatening and stuff.
I am shocked that his wife, we put up with that shit
and I hope she's okay.
That was pretty bad.
I mean, wow.
Was that bad?
He peeped all out of the gun and pointed at the audience.
Yeah, that's pretty bad.
Well, you know, I was at the on the fat stick lookalike drinking cracker juice
I've had worse, you know, this
Somebody that really came really close to my house and said that they were in a grape and kill me. Oh my god
I'm so sorry guy. Yeah, he said that. Oh my god. Yeah, I'm gonna spank him for that
That's not appropriate.
No, he's not far and same with the exile guy.
Well, but I hate him.
I hate exile.
He said he was he actually cut himself off
because he doesn't even know me.
So he doesn't even know that I already tracked his ass down.
He better watch his mother fucking better.
He better.
So.
I mean some of these people are just guys guys we're dealing with some actual mental patient. I mean that guy
Exiled one exiled one the British guy. He's fine, but do you have the guy the southern accent?
Got his name. Oh my god
You know what's so crazy is he's not very far from me at all
There's I mean there's some sick people. He's like he's like
Not far from me
I'll tell you that he's not far. Okay. Well, we're gonna find us in 20 miles
We're gonna I'm gonna find him. I'm gonna I'm gonna track him down
I already know where he's at and I already know and everybody does so like my brother
And he's done and so does my dad dude yeah dad lives right too close to him for comfort I'll tell you this and
I know my dad is like so dangerous to give you a smile right now. Who's this coming backstage? Who's this?
Is it 300 blow you're okay? He's done. Okay. I do have something to show you guys
I just want to show you this real quick, and this is just a it's only a minute long. This is really quick
And I hope you laugh and second it's coming
Here you go. Watch this real quick.
The Mercury. The Mercury is a song.
Oh, I'm Peter. I'm Peter.
Ah!
Ahhhh!
Hey, stop it, Psyche.
Oh my gosh. Look at you, Psyche.
You want a future, you want to sing a song, you'll be about your best.
You want a future, there you go.
There, you can see the pictures, there you go.
Oh my gosh, this is so funny.
Yeah, you gotta cut the song.
Yeah, I cut the song out.
Okay, what was the most, what am I saying?
Didn't work. Oh
It's so cute, but yeah, you got to cut the song because the fucking you know what I mean
Hey, I make it good Michael Jackson though. I think I make it good Michael Jackson
R.I.P. Michael Jackson.
Chris, you're my friend Danny.
He's really cute.
She has three times at a gas station.
You told me that.
That's so insane because you know what?
I had
this lady
that I watched
that I've been watching her for years.
And her son
went out there and he
actually was at that scene.
At the gas station with Danny. Yes or shit, but he was down the street
They said that it happened at the gas station and that it ended at
It said that he robbed somebody and then he didn't rob anybody
He's not he didn't he was on a stream. He went to the gas station some guy like was either shadowing him
I don't know if like someone did he didn't he wasn't a he wasn't a robber. He wasn't that's what they said
That's what you know, I've watched all the news
He didn't he wasn't a thief like he wouldn't go rob his like neighbor gas station that was so close
We hear the gun but he said they said that he pulled a gun on a child
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
God, I was like, no, no, it wasn't yeah, my friend Danny. I mean, I can show you I did like okay
So I dance did I dance that guy's name was Danny to the same gay
Oh, yeah, it's weird. Well, it's the same day. It was two weeks ago, but I made a little video. This is like a little memorial
No, I remember you saying that and then that guy you said that this guy got shot and then that's what that guy happened in Florida
It's like a weird coincidence about that, but this is I wish you I play this. I'm so sorry
Okay, you know, it's okay, but I played this on for day
This is just him. It's a short song that I made from about how like, you know, he danced for me once and stuff
I just want to play this for you guys a little memorial for him
And I know it's sad for some people, and sorry,
it's that for me too.
But I just like to remember the good times,
and this is like a good time for him.
So this is Danny, and I made this song for him and stuff.
That's really sweet, that's really nice.
And I think you'll like it.
I think it's a funny song actually, here you go.
This is a, he looked like Kid Rock,
there he is right there.
And it's a recipe, it's Danny, right?
Yeah, R-I-P.
Then it's stranger walking in like a county fair star
Looking so cute got that kid rock guitar bar
I'm making the only ass shit
But my brain's yelling open, I'm made your way
He did one little dance and my soul said fine
Now I'm losing my dignity, one beat at a time
I don't hit him up much, I keep it tight
Cause he's got that charm that can wreck my night
One smile on hay, and I'm already sure
He'll talk me into something expensive
I want to buy your underwear and your socks in a pack. Oh my gosh
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my tracks and no he ain't gay so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling
I don't talk to him much cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
I don't even ever bike dude
Wow!
He got that I might be a problem grand Like he's selling sunshine with a citizen
He laughs, I fold my wallet, get scared I'm tryna play cool, but I'm deeply unprepared
I'm not sayin' I'm obsessed Just molly the range like who needs self-respect
When the vibes is strange I keep my distance, I do my best
But he pops in my head like a bad text
he says we should hang i'm black maybe soon then i'll hide in my house like a raccoon dan is stranger
your trouble your cutie tag i want to buy your underwear and your socks and a pack you dance for
me once now i'm down bad facts but i'm keeping it casual i'm losing my tracks and oh we ain't
You talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
And I don't even have a bike to
I'm a responsible adult allegedly, but that man says babe and my brain goes
This man really do you say that?
I'm not his plan. I'm just a humble fan with a morally questionable stance if he blinks twice
I'm making poor choices hearing cash registers like back
Wow
I'm really into it
I can't do this
And Jamie! Crystal!
Oh my gosh, it's our beautiful Jamie!
And I don't even have a butt, dude.
Shout out to Jenny.
Remember to have a butt.
Money.
And shout out to Jamie.
Eric, get up here.
Please stop being adorable.
Stop being adorable.
We love our Jamie butt.
It's like, this is really hard.
I know it's hard.
It's hard.
Sorry.
It's so sad.
It is sad.
But and he was so nice and I didn't make him happy by like you say he was talking about you Jamie. Oh
Well, hey, Jamie's here. Jamie's Cowboys is here. Thanks for coming up. Jamie. I love Jamie. Jamie. Jamie is a beautiful
Kid hear me. Yeah, we hear you
I'm sorry your boyfriend. I'm sorry your boyfriend got mad. I'm sorry. Hey, but you know what?
It's like a little bit quieter now Aaron and I'm sorry about the Aaron. I'm sorry
It was a little bit crazy, but yeah
Yeah, we're up here. We heard you Jamie. How are you Jamie? Jamie told me the news about it
Like she's like someone told me your friend passed away last night, and I was like, oh my gosh
Because I saw I just saw his stream was on last night, and so I thought it was like I can't hear you my phone
I'll be right back. Okay. I thought it was I thought it was like a bet
You know, I've heard someone said joke around a lab
Yeah, we hear you hear me
She's there. Oh, I hear you. Yeah
I think she's coming back. I don't think we could hear you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Everybody does and especially Christine. Oh,
Here she is. Here she is. Here she is.
know psyche we can hear you yeah you can hear everybody but psyche I'll fix it
yeah yeah I hear it but now but you know earlier when I was joining it was like
I could hear everybody but psyche does Jamie sleep when she farts hey oh my
thing that is this is Jamie I can hear you all my gosh baby I'm so sorry it's
Hey, you know what we're all friends and uh, and I know you guys like supported him too and like
He was really happy when the chat went over. Do you ever say hi to him Jamie?
Do you ever get a chance to say hi to him? A couple of times
Yeah, and then Alain was in here a site a couple days ago, so that was good
Yeah, and we I knew I do have some friends coming over and saying hi to me and I appreciate that and stuff and we can all like
Remember the good times. He was a good person. I mean, it's like, you know, he wasn't perfect
like like we all have like not there aren't imperfect moments, but he was always nice to me and
You know, I think he didn't deserve to go out the way he did, you know, he shot three times in the chest
Yeah
But I do believe, you know
In an afterlife and I believe like I feel a spirit. I do feel a spirit from time to time
He got shot three times and what the hell I think he went to this local gas station
You can hear on the stream. He had a stream on and stuff. You can hear him go
It's hard it's hard it's hard hard hard to see it. Yeah, it's hard, but you know what I hope he's
Why God takes
Right, it's angels. Well, we're all gonna go sometime, you know, and it's like, you know
He's gonna be forever young like like some people like Marilyn Monroe and see the people that died
He's a god taking when somebody does something so terrible. Mm-hmm. I don't know. I don't know. There's not gonna
Sometimes a good yeah, sometimes the worst you know, but it's like he was a good person and I do believe like
Like I remember like a few weeks like he was all and on God of course is gonna be taking I'm not saying Matt
I'm saying like he he was just in his jeep site. Like yeah, he was I was talking to him in his car
Actually, he had hit a fan like no, you know, um buy him like car parts and stuff like that
Actually, he got in his little red robe. He was he got
He was in his like little red robe and he had his cat
And stuff and it was like and he was happy and stuff
But I knew there was something off a little bit
He was on all the time and then he was like kind of like not spurging out, but he was like
Little bit lashing out at the audience and stuff and I was like hey
I'm gonna send my audience there one night
He said he was in it if I got a hundred people in there
He's gonna give me a kiss and stuff. I got I got 40 people in there
So maybe he'll kiss me on the cheek or something like that
But I do maybe I do feel like a little kiss on the cheek. I don't know and he wasn't gay
I know it wasn't gay. I don't want to offend anybody or anything like that, but right a dance for me once
And into his in his boxers the name he was his mod for a night
And then the next day he started charging me every five dollars every time I hit on him
I think he got to like five hundred dollars and then I like left this chat
While and then I came back and he had forgotten about it. It was perfect
I love you Danny. I love that was a stupid joke and whatever, but I love you Danny
I love you when I got that text message. I was like wait what no, you know
It's
It's terrible regardless. It's sad. It's fucking
It's brutal dude. I don't think I don't think you're as much Christina at all because because charisma is like way too cool
It just took me a while to give him that message when I got the text
So and I didn't believe it and I was like that I've gotten those messages before this person is not like I got Apollo's dead
I got I'm Joker's dead and oh like I wouldn't do that because it came from the big
I know you did I know you wasn't you but I mean I have gotten those messages
And I and so but but sometimes on YouTube, they you know, the person's not really dead and stuff
Who's charisma? It's a mystery, you know, charisma is a mystery, but you know what charisma has always been a hundred percent of the time a
Not a mystery is Jamie
You're such a great person and thanks
She is
Everyone loves Jamie, and I don't know why Bita and salmon are picking on Jamie and stuff like that. I have no idea
I don't know because Jamie's Jamie's always just a sweet person
I'm talking about it has nothing to do with that Katie
No, okay. Thanks. Nothing.
Nothing. It's a totally different Katie.
Yes, we're cool Mace.
Crystal, she's incredible though, by the way.
But no, it has nothing to do with that Katie though.
Right, right. But the other...
I just want to throw that out there.
It's a different Katie I think she's talking about.
And then there's a few, there's a few Katie's and stuff in the...
Yeah, this Katie used to...
She like love chop dude. And then she's like denying that she loved chop. But then they're saying that she was one of that girls. Okay. Remember blogger. Remember blogger dated like this young girl.
Right. Yeah.
Okay, Katie is supposed to be her sister apparently. I don't fucking know
I don't really want to find a blogger dated. I know a blogger dated this woman
I think she was 18 years old or something on the panel versus I heard Katie was her sister your younger sister that was underage
and that is the same profile picture and I don't know if it's sure or not, but I'm not there and I'm not
critiquing everything okay
Through easy I think but I don't think charisma is a big fan of his and she's a little bit
She was a little bit of a critic, but she was always she's always been a good mod
I don't think she's involved in any of some of the stuff we're talking about so
No, we're not talking about the same Katie's. We're not even talking about
You know, you know, you know, and and and Jamie's like today
Like they're trying to give me to talk and I was like, no, I told Jamie. Oh, thank you, psych. I'm not so I'm gonna try
But Jamie, Jamie, you are amazing.
I have never, I don't think I've ever said anything.
Yeah, I don't think you have either.
I would never say like, unless you were like saying some shit to me and Chad,
I just like react, but do that.
Yeah, it's not it's not the same. It's not the same person. And so yeah, we're all good. Hey, yeah, but no
I knew I told everybody right away that was not the same Katie and don't you guys so like
Fucking try to throw that Katie against me because that Katie
Uh, might hate me because she's friends with the clumsy
That's exactly what I said
I'm not sure I don't think it's the same Katie game. I'm not I don't think but let's let's change this topic
But because I have no problems with Katie. I said if you're talking about
My Katie she might hate me because I have a problem with clumsy
Has a problem with her. Okay
Here comes is here and uh, let's all be respectful
Nothing do a clumsy. It doesn't even have anything to do a clumsy
Did you ever watch that a that last alien movie it was still good
Yeah, Romulus Romulus, I haven't seen it with Chrismas you have a problem with mass and Gil
Not not the douche, but the the woman in chat
Sorry
Jamie is clumsy say hi hi clumsy
What's up clumsy are you there? Oh, Jamie, but I'm so happy for you Jamie you're doing so good
Or at the moment message. Thank you
Yeah, Jamie is recovering, you know, she had a bad traffic, she got into a bad car accident
Yeah, I'm relearning everything words and everything and how to do things over again, but I'm here
late
Yeah, and you're doing
Really great. I mean she's like she's learning, you know, sometimes if you're you know
We learned some things as babies and stuff and it's like we learned things as the baby mind and we're learning stuff
Sometimes we were learned stuff as in it as with the adult mind and so maybe she's learning things better, you know, right?
Can you hear me now?
Yeah, I had to learn my P's and Q's a little bit every day again.
I didn't listen to my P's and Q's.
Because these people are so disrespectful to me.
I am really a respectful person.
I do not.
I would not disrespect people in real life because I could give them face to face.
I would not be like mean or anything like that.
Talking out, you know what I mean, but I am very forceful and
You know as as far as that wise
The glow is not coming back. There's no gonna be no gun shown. Well, it's like uh,
Like ongoing still concussion i'm dealing with so there's words that I get confused like have I heard those before but i'm
i'm getting there
I think I have that as well because I was in quite a few accidents and I still wonder
because they're like, oh, you did all your therapy and you just aced everything, you
know, but I didn't feel great, you know, about everything, even though they were like, oh,
you're great.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I can't believe the simplest things were me out still.
I know somebody that tells me that I'm supposed to do that, so yeah, I am.
Yeah
That's a different one says Jamie always is a kind person
That's your mason or you know, you're gonna love Jamie I mean it's like me mason mason. Oh, yeah, but we have an elder coming up
Let's welcome elder to the show
Eldo, Jamie, you're the best person though.
I I I'm locked with an elbow.
Hand down.
What upside Jamie Clumsy?
Eldo, how are you?
Eldo. I'm good.
Crystal, I got a question.
When are you going to come back to Sandman?
Don't don't you miss a man?
No, I will never.
You know how I am, Nick.
once you fucking turn on me I'm done dude you disrespect my feelings or you
actually he was my friend and then he started doing really mean things to me
it's a whole different story and although although I was telling time
tonight you're not black and he was like yes he's black I know for sure I was
like I've seen him twerk
He's not he's not black. Are you black? Just tell me tell her what's up for all the time?
Each works like this
What do you do for you he apologized to me that's sweet, you know what an elbow
I'm sorry, we've got our ups and downs, Eldo, and I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry if I said something wrong about you and I you know, I'm sorry. I apologize
So you cannot use me as like a like this it does not work like this
Hey, we're having a hug fest right now
This is called a hug box panel and I want to give everyone a big hug right now. I love you guys, okay?
I'm saying you apologize to me remember a lot like remember you guys were trying to kill me off on
Crystal crystal come back crystal come back come back crystal come back
Remember when crystal remember when you got abducted by the X-files aliens
Can you not hear me I hear you
We all hear you. Okay. Well
Remember when the aliens came down rigid demon get up here, too. Yeah, right? No, I do not know
You were talking about we were talking about aliens and stuff and the the Christine stuff
Aliens came and picked you up with me
Oh funny why is I have no idea
Remember when we got abducted by the aliens and then you were laughing when I was getting amily probed. I
Do not but I'm sure it sounds hilarious was hilarious. It was I was crying
But you were laughing at heart you were you're pointing at me laughing when I was getting amily probed by the aliens
It was because you're always sexual. I'm sure you loved it. Why did like it? I did like it. Okay aliens
Yeah, can you come back aliens? This is not what we were talking about. Okay. I'm so sorry. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
You guys talk. I'm gonna get under the blanket with the cat you guys talk you guys talk
But yeah, can aliens I need to get a nearly probed again. I'm really low
Thank you. Okay. Well, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but I need an anal probe step
It needs to be groped in his
booty hole.
Yeah.
My booty hole is cold.
It's cold.
I need that thermometer in there with a little bit of a lube.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
I'm going to set up.
I want to say this.
I also did apologize to me and I've always said that although
apologized to me and I accept that and I fucking love you.
even though I'm not the greatest person for people,
I know we're to hang in the lake to land and throw you.
I fuck with you, Crystal, you know what I'm saying?
I don't like what, I don't like what Samman did to you,
but at the same time, you know,
he's trying to, you know, make it up to you.
So, you know.
Oh, he can never make it up to me.
Okay, you like you like clumsy clumsy you you never take the same man back
I was talking last night for like hours. Then today I was on his panel. Christine, are you sure you never talked to like Samion?
And then he said, then he said, I said, Oh, come to my show. I'm going to ask when he was wrapping up.
What's that? What's that, Chris?
Do you talk to fucking Sam and I've never had you know how I even know Sam man
Because I started hacking his big home, Isaiah
Hey, I love Zia though. That was on Zia's show last night.
I know you wasn't about to say you don't mind Zaya.
I don't mind Zaya.
He's cute and he's nice and leaves Zaya alone.
I have no idea who those people are.
Zaya and Pebs.
I don't mind them.
Don't know.
Okay, well, Peb, it's way nicer to me than a lot of other motherfuckers.
Hey, all I'll say is I was like, I want to lick your butt hole, Zaya, and he's like, show me how you're going to do it.
And I did, and he's like, what?
Let's go.
Well, then here we go.
Yeah, okay, I'm going to shut up. I'm going to go to bed.
I'm going to go to bed.
It's not like it's something new.
Jamie, is this for you?
No, he was nice. He was cool. He was where you ain't you it was it was guys
You guys know Jamie. Is that Jamie? That's Jamie's cowboy
We know Jamie
Jamie I just want to make sure is you
Jamie are you cool?
Jamie I know I don't mean to be weird and stuff like that the pebs and zea were really nice to me
And not everyone's very nice to me, and they were just cool and nice and so I love to say
I don't know the history. I only know is Alexander mayors calls him
He's my trafficker. She calls me a trafficker. I mean, I can't really judge people based on what Alexander mayors says anymore
You know just with truck my channel the bitch. Okay, so that's it
And I'm not gonna sit here and be like beat on but like oh my god, like you're fucking talking to the person
I don't like it really
Everyone has their own
Relationships with people their opinions about what happens and stuff like that. I mean if he does something that bad
I think he'd probably be in prison and stuff, but I think I mean but but check this out though. How do you?
I don't even want to talk about it, okay?
Oh, Clumsy, Clumsy, you got proof that she told you
why you're talking to this person?
Is it through text or was it through phone calls?
Hold on, what do you mean?
Why is she was telling you not to talk to certain people?
I mean
Shappin with fucking J-Dog bro, and look she thinks that me and J-Dog were close like
Where do you see J-Dog always on my panel or all we you know, I'm saying like
That's that day that she tried to make me fucking pick sides bro because that beef she had with him
Yeah, they always but she always does but you know what and then she has J dog on her show and then she they flirt
You are a fucking site taker. You are always was doing some weird shit with fucking Karen
Started talking to Karen
She was on your piano. That's what she was. That's what Chris is saying.
You guys found out how badass my family were and scared as fuck. Okay, don't you even deny
You guys look me up try to find out some shit and found out you might get fucked
Wow, let's fucking play it real
About that. You found out that I'm a badass and you're scared as fuck
Crystal crystal scares me sometimes
Real-life badass people in my family that are badass more badass than I could ever
My family some of my family were for the government doing fighter drones. Exactly. I got weight. I got both sides
I got double
Move out the country. I got in and out. I got bad and good. Okay. Let me tell you there now
We're okay. Well, what do you mean bad though? What do you mean?
Like you got bad people like what do you mean? I mean, I don't think she means like that bad
I mean and maybe like, you know, hold on hold on. No, no, no, let her answer
Crystal what do you mean by that? No, I'm just saying what about your bad? What? No, no, no, I want you good
Crystal I know what she means though clarify clarify
We could do bad or good
I guess protectors just people that are willing to fight for her and stuff, right Crystal
Yeah
Bad we could do either
So crystal you don't like Karen is that what you're saying? I mean, I love Karen. I like Karen too
Karen's a nice lady. I mean, it's like I have no problem with Karen at all
They're both nice to me, I mean it's like they're both I mean it's like I can come to an agreement about
I get along with both of them. Do I have a problem with Karen in excess? No. They're problem with crystalline. No
Do they have a problem with each other? Yeah, but
They're problem with Alexandra and and you know Karen get a charge because of me. I don't know who gets charged
Attorney that watches my fucking everything on my shit, dude
I have somebody that keeps track of all your fucking bullshit because I got a badass family
Yeah, me too. Me too.
I mean, and that's good.
I mean, I'm sure all of us have badass family.
You know, clumsy, you know.
I don't think they do, actually.
Well, clumsy, I think he has badass family.
I think Jamie's, I don't know about Jamie's family,
but she's got me.
Jamie definitely probably does,
because Jamie's a badass family.
I think I'm Jamie's family.
And it's like, so she's connected to the bad asses too.
Crystal Marie, you got bad asses,
money for 20, I wouldn't fuck with anybody up here.
We're all good.
I think everyone's up here is a good person.
And we are protectors internet gangster is another story for a
Life that you never lived you're in a different fucking country by the way
Our country and say that to me in our fucking country
You know what let's go ahead and let you speak more in your own country and see how far you go
I write
What can't I say I love you to a person without them saying just laugh is it his mic?
He's just a bitch. He's being a bitch money for 20. I'm sorry. You're being a bitch. I'm sorry. Okay
Clumsy Jamie
Psyche
Yeah, I don't know. I love you. I love you crystal
Crystal can I give you a hug?
We're giving each other hugs. Hey psyche. That's what what's up training and I don't really need to know it for
Okay, Jamie. I love you. Jamie has to
She did yeah, she was he can't hear right although and I again, although I'm sorry and
Have you I thought you hated me for a little bit and you were like I'm talking shit
And so I react to that stuff, you know, I'm I get triggered
But I never felt at your I still played the song big big yellow the trucker and stuff like that
I never like told Alexander about you and I don't I wouldn't okay, so um, well, maybe I said you were trucker
That was all I said
I'm sorry for you saying that
but you say it yourself
Did you say he's a fucker or a trucker?
I said both
Oh my god
Well everybody, oh my gosh, you fucking told on him twice
Yeah, well he told on me twice
I said you're a fucker and a trucker
But I didn't know
guys
So what would you say earlier before you cut off about a Sandman and the panel and
Yeah, Sam and I didn't use me as content last night
I was like here. I was this thumbnail plus me saying the n-word that's everyone's shocked and offended then today
I got kicked off. He'd give a discount on me for I was only one on camera by the way
He gave a discount. It says $17 kicks like he off Christine and kicked me off and then
I went to his panel today, and I did but I did a bunch of n-word
Let me tell you one thing. He hates Christine. Okay
Saman hates Christine
He fucking hates her dude and we can bond over that me to like like you like wants me to hang out
Thank you. Her name is not even her name is not Christine by the way guys
I know her name is not it's not even Christine and then she's like saying
Oh, Psyche, you're saying I kill babies.
Hey, Joni, what's up, girl?
Hey, Joni, we're having a good, Joni.
But we're not doing that.
Well, can we not?
Hey, hey, I want to say, hey, my friend Joni.
Joni is so amazing to you.
I love Joni for you.
I love, I don't know Joni, but I love that you, like.
She's amazing.
I've heard you talk about your friends and I like it.
Do you have amazing people around me?
She is awesome.
Yes, she is.
The link will be dropped and who's like Jamie when Jamie is around, you know, it was like
Jamie's so sweet and like the best. Who is this?
Y'all ever get tired of talking in circles. Is that an alien? Who's the alien?
Move an alien on the panel. I get that you're talking in circles. Can I suck your dick alien?
Hello, I'll never get anywhere close to my dick
But why but you ain't only probe me and I can't suck your dick
You didn't you
Who is this he thinks he had a life before like a streamer
But nobody knows
I'm very very drunk. I'm sorry
Because
Yeah, he's trying to steal your views. Just let him just kick him alien. Are you trying to steal my views?
What would I need your views? Who is this you're really alien, right?
Sound like saying the honest war dog. It's a sticky war war dog. Get up here. Come on. You want sexy get up here
We're dog
Don't need he's trying to steal your views because he wants to be he really like he tried hey. Hey guess what?
Listen, Psyche, a fucking war dog has tried to redo his channel and be somebody again like 20 times and he cannot get four viewers.
War dog, War dog, War dog, do you want me to help you with your channel?
I don't need no help with growing any channels.
If I wanted to talk in circle, that'd be a different story.
You talk in my circle, my anal circle.
No, there's gonna be no anal circles.
Please?
Sorry, thank you.
Okay, guys, you lied. It was a joke. It was a joke.
That's why he's here.
He's here to get his shit ripped open, bro.
Oh, my God.
You're gonna do it clumsy
You want me to that guy listen?
War dog has no
Because he poofed in his panties
Poops in his panties
You're saying or doc boot his pants again, okay
Who's this?
What?
My god, who is that?
See if your dick comes out tonight or whatever it is you're in trouble see
You're in trouble, okay, I don't have a vagina
It looks like one to me
I don't have a vagina.
Hey, hey, why did you do the helicopter?
It looked like a little, it looked like a propeller.
Siggi, we got wheeled.
That's what you said.
That's not what I said.
You did the helicopter for me backstage,
and it looked like...
like a little propeller on like a little
this is what you said
this is your words
not mine
your words not mine
disgusting um infected
penis
it was like
it was like that
could you be more specific
yeah don't
it was like a cessna
What model Cessna
Breaks and it bleeds if it which no, no, no, I'm asking for a specific
We hear you now. Oh perfect
Sorry guys, that was too much. It's okay. SIG is too much for me
I didn't want to say that about SIG
I really hate to see them because I'm really curious about it because I never heard nothing about this
No, you're so do it. Crystal join my discord and I'll send you a picture of his vagina
He showed it. I don't want to see it and I don't want to join your discord
I didn't want to see it either, but he showed it
And he didn't know I'm not down
He didn't tell her for me to it was disgusting. No
It was really bad and I was like, hey, I want to see a propeller anybody was but it was not
asking good times
He said that he tries to pull his Marcy Marcy come up Marcy
We need some more feminine
Can you guys listen to me for one second?
You're the same weirdos talking about someone pulling their dick out while you show your
Shut up
Yeah
Nobody cares, okay, he is like me everybody and like
Joni is that you say you put it put in the search egg plant. That's what you use
You say
Siggi told us
Is that is the dick bleeds when he moves? Oh my god. Okay. This is too much. It's a little too much information
I don't want to hear that. I don't want to hear that. That's what he told you crystal
You got the egg
Guys, we got the eggplants in the chat.
Joni, Joni, if you want to come up.
I love you to come up too.
We got Jamie here.
We got Eldil, I love you, sorry.
We're just having fun.
We're just having a little fun.
If you want to come up, if you don't, it's fine.
I'm just having fun.
Oh, Joni, come on.
Joni, I'm sure you're so sweet and fun.
Aw, she is.
She is, she is, she is.
Totally.
Hey, I know the best people.
I really, I really.
I know you really do actually psyche I've always told you that you have a great you know I've
always said this you really need to let the bad people out
Yeah, I know and let the good people in she she I think she's considering it Joni
I promise you we got a good. We got good people. We have clumsy Jamie's Cowboys
We have Eldo and Crystal Marie and everyone is she okay Joni use the corn instead of the egg
Why did I kick four dogs because we're all being a bitch. He's just be his whining. I'll let him back on but we're
Are you just gonna wine?
Who was whining?
You were you I think you've got to confuse psych. You're the one that's always whining. Oh
Oops, I just dropped him again. I'm so sorry
Hey, hey, we're done. We're done
I'm sure war dog has a lot to say about me, but let me talk about war dog for a second
He's sitting a chair for about five years
Legs are smaller than my arms. Okay, and I'm really skinny arms
So okay, that is saying a while Johnny. I do need you. I don't know if they work or not
I don't know what I'm asking you. I'm asking you to be mean
I love you, Jo. If Joanie wants to come up, she can, she doesn't want to come up.
Psych, I just wanted to ask Elda if I was ever rude, because I forget sometimes before like,
like after the wreck, you know, things happen before, so I just want to apologize.
You're running away? She's running. No, I'm not running away.
No, no, no, Joanie's running away. Joanie, don't run away.
I just want to apologize if I ever was. Yeah.
You're good, you're good, Jamie.
Yeah.
Can you accept the apology?
And Marcy, I want you to come up too if you can.
I think I need some more feminine, balanced energy.
We have like two women.
We have four strong masculine personalities.
Do you know what else are you doing down there?
Erin, Erin.
Marcy was going a lot.
She's the one with like the color hair, right?
Like the short color hair.
Marcy has the colored hair, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, midnight, the reason why I want to ask that is.
Oh, midnight.
I forget that.
I don't see midnight in chat, but I love.
Midnight midnight midnight thinking complaining because I blocked midnight because midnight's called me a recharge or something
Like I don't like when people call me a recharge. It is a fun
Yeah, but I'll let up a lot, but I said I'm too strong to like listen. I'm gonna tell you right now
Alex better not fucking hide me
I try to look over an hour and it was a nightmare to the game thing that is unblocked and stuff
So midnight tomorrow. I'll look at my
I'll get it, I'll get it figured out. Okay. Be honest tonight. It's my only person.
Just being your alt. Yes. Yes.
It's actually right here. Even more dog. We have good people here and I'd like I love all you guys.
Okay. I don't just like you. I love you. Okay. And that's from the bottom of my heart. I love you.
Daylight rises. Thank you. Yeah.
a war dog used to have sex with beta war dog is that true on stream on the
stream yeah doc scene in the chat no doc no doc doc scene in the chat but war dog
you had sex with beta on the stream
Are we talking about Chris are we talking about crystal Marie that have had sex with Aldi 1k in clumsy that
Oh my god
go
And he's got some
In project deflect project deflect project. Yeah, you fucking faggot you fucking
Had another ass old lady you said she was pregnant by the way and when you were fucking around with fucking beta
Dude, you fucked that whole shit up.
Hey, guys, it's Christine.
Hey, it's Christine, guys.
I want candy.
Yeah, you were obsessed.
You would be a lovey-tallyer.
Wow
Wow guys, I'm so you're the same person that was in my discord, right?
And you showed me your tits no problem, right? Find your discord. I'm not in I've never been in a discord
He's stupid retard. All right, Crystal. You better find Chris land, buddy
You're a drunk join mine
Crystal you're welcome at all our discords. We want yeah, I'm not in I haven't been in a discord since
Tilla left streaming years ago
So so crystal not to be no, you know disrespectful, but have you ever shown your your tits?
Yeah, I never saw crystals tits. No, I'm just that in general
I'm not trying to say
There was like a time. It was it was pretty wild
She took a shower in front of good times because he said he was dying of cancer
No, no, I went I was hanging out with the good times and he I don't know like my phone
You're calling
The same thing in front of Sam and I took a photo I took a shower my speedo and then Sam man
I think jerked off to me
No, it was a totally different situation
It was different a little bit
but salmon no, I was getting ready. I had no idea I was being recorded
It just like a water drop hit the phone in it. It turned out. It's everybody. It happens and he man
I love you and he man. Hey, man. I hate me. Hey, man. Hey, man. You hate me and stuff. Hey, man
You're like you're like one of my top. I don't have any
You see you 20 20s here guys. We have the whole gang is together. Let me tell you
about the situation.
Let's hear it. Let's hear it. I want to hear it.
The situation.
The situation. Hey, guys.
I'm ready.
Okay.
Hold on. Okay. That guy? Okay. Which guy?
Which one?
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Dot guy.
I felt like showing them one time.
What's dot guy? Tell me dot guy's name again.
Um, this is, um, War Dog, Jamie's Cowboys, Eldo, Clumsy, and...
Thank you. Thank you. War Dog. War Dog. Okay. Thank you.
Dot, uh, nothing, um, dot com dot nothing dot com. Um, thank you so much.
I had to remember, I think, uh, that guy was like a sickle path and he was having, like,
he was trying to, like, okay, you know that SIG had this old lady and girlfriend.
So you had an old lady girlfriend tell me more and
Well, see this guy was trying to mess up the relationship
So he would send that lady like dick pics and stuff. Oh wait, but he has a vagina though
Be to the entire time
he literally has a vagina
I
Cannot tell you he doesn't he has AIDS legs
Dude the guy is six foot on he has skinnier legs and anybody that ever was born
Crystal Marie was that was that females name a war kitty
Oh, yes. Yes, we're kidding that he tried to mess with more dog and
Are they a cute couple we're talking more kitty sounds like a cute couple. Are they gonna know he okay?
I want to hear well, he was with this other chick and then he messed up
That was Siggi's girlfriend. That was six girl. We had a girl
I don't believe this yet for years. He had her for five years
Five years
Newster guess what he met war kitty, and then he hit her. Oh, no, okay
Let's not make allegations unless I really it's not really bad allegations. Okay?
We're gonna have fun.
Everybody.
Go ahead, go ahead, you just talk.
Oh, I'm gonna shut up, I'm gonna shut up.
I gotta go pee.
Can somebody fill in for the rest of it?
Yes, someone come up.
I'm gonna post the link again.
Can someone come up?
I really, I do need some help.
Someone can come up.
Clumsy, you know the story, didn't he hit her?
War dog kitty
So I'm telling you the truth. I promise to
And his parents even kicked him out
Please
I know she doesn't but it's like I don't necessarily want everybody's
Dirty laundry aired here. I want to like I want this more to be like a place a safe place. Don't lie
Let's be safe. Come on. Come on crystal. Let's be a little safe
And he man, I'm sorry. Hey, man, you hate me. It's okay. It's okay
Wasn't wasn't he man up be the mug?
Yeah, he man's be this bond to and he man talks so much. Oh, he's still there. Okay. Oh, he was talking
It's a woman. It's a woman. Oh, see, I'm sorry. He man. I mean damn. I mean look at the names
You mean three to glow you can't come back on the show cuz you put a gun it you put a little bit of gun in here
I don't care because you can pick it up in a second
You put a gun in your mouth and to the stream and it's not appropriate. Okay
You can't be you. You can't be back on tonight at least not tonight. Okay. You're staying off the show
I'm sorry. I have to be a dick. I'm sorry. Jamie. What were you were you? Go ahead. Jamie. Jamie you talk
No, no, no, that's okay. It's like go ahead. Okay. Who's talking crystal? You were telling a story about a warlock
Yeah, crystal is
Crystal go ahead. You can finish it
I think she went to go tinkle
Oh, she went to the big peak.
Clumsy went to NFC side.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
Uh, see, I knew I was going to get some shit for wearing it.
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
I knew it.
Hey, at least you have rumble.
You should put that away in a glass case, like all mine.
Like they're all put away.
Rumble.
Massengill.
Midnight is Massengill.
Um, gilly, Massengilly weed.
Pitter.
I, I, I hid them because they have been.
No docs.
Oh, no.
That's their name in the chat.
Massengilly weed.
Oh.
They're actually named after her douche and stuff, but she's a nice person though. Yep
She is I like midnight, but midnight you're gonna come back tomorrow
You tell Alex he better not do that again. Yeah. Oh Alex
Never if I hear you saying I want candy with Christine or
Candy
And Christine
Everyone's saying you look good in that bathing suit. It was being nice
You look horrible
Well, they said that she
They thought that she was like eighty or seventy or she was lying about her age
All I heard is that she was lying about her age. No, she is
Maybe if she
Was lying about her age. She is lying. She's a liar because her name's not even Christine and then she's mad
Oh, you said I was sacrificing babies in the woods. Your name is Christine. Her name's not her name's not even Christine
She's she has another name miss Katrina. I
Didn't say it. I didn't say it. I didn't say it. I didn't say it. But anyway
Christine
Don't
I don't want to see you in Bikini again, nor singing an Aaron Carter song.
So you see another name in chat, you know, like that other bitch is the same bitch.
And I'm telling you, El, Eldo Clemsi, whatever, whoever, that knows Jamie, everybody.
I mean, actually, everybody.
Oh, just be, be, be, be in a, be in a massing guilt tonight, um, in that it was mass, you're
massing guilt tonight.
Christina is Christine. I know, I figured it out, because Christine told me one time,
didn't tell me, but she said, oh my name starts with a K, I have an alt. And then it was always
Katrina. Katrina blogged you? Well, Katrina is a great mod, but Christine is a bad mod.
But maybe
Personality
I'm thinking that that that lady has a like double personalities or I think there's more than a double
I think it's I think it's like a they like
Herman's head is that kind of situation, right? Yeah, I
She heard, you know her family hates her
I don't let's not get I don't want to get
Like hates her god
I don't want to slander Christine even I mean, we don't have to she did it to herself because
Literally told me to jump off a bridge and
into alligator infested waters and that she meant it.
Well, you don't have to, like, because that's exactly why,
because, you know, why normal people would never tell people that.
And I would never do that.
I would never, I want, if she wants to go on a, on a trip and sponsor me,
I will bridge jump with her, but she said it's fun.
That lady is a different kind of evil.
We might joke around and have like little jokes, but we don't fucking want nobody to actually hurt them
She said she wants me to actually
This old lady actually loves the idea like she's a sicko. She's Epstein filed
I we send me a ticket to Epstein Island and was like you'll come get a massage
I was like, I know that sounds like trouble. So I didn't go who said that Christine. Oh
Yeah
Oh crystal, you don't like Christine. Of course not
And she invited me to the island and I said I can't go
On YouTube the Christina and everyone's chat. She said her sister's Gillis St. Maxwell
I said nothing about the bitch for weeks and then she started harassing me again as soon as Sam and started saying I had a nice body she was like so she must be doing BMS or something I don't know but she literally said that I'm not doing BMS
She said her Chris name is Christine Maxwell.
So Gillesana is her sister.
She said she works for Mossad, and her father was killed.
One dog, you're a dreamer.
And she invited me to the island.
Dream on, buddy.
You're a faggot dreamer.
Hey, Crystal.
Oh, sorry.
Every time you're on a stream, you
show your body looking for attention.
It asks word.
I did not show my body.
But when did I show my body, Psyche?
I saw, I just saw your belly when we did this.
When we did this little belly.
Along, that was, he said every single time I come on,
I show my body.
He said.
Every single time, sometimes she doesn't.
Yeah, no, it's true. Christina got our kids hooked on drugs on purpose. I think what I didn't believe it's true
I think it's true. Yeah, you know her son hates her guts. Oh my god
And I'm in Christine guys. This is a fake Christine. Okay. It's a fake Christine
So
She made herself Christina
Visual character, this is all for him perversus only. This is a joke guys
Have a sense of humor for seeing
Gross set of balls, okay?
We're not joking around now because Christine likes to go serious and say it really and try to...
Oh, she got it. Oh, she got it. She told me. She told me to kill myself.
She actually told me to kill myself.
She had the ability to ruin my job. She said she has license in Missouri and she can 151 me.
Okay, let's see it. Oh, it's called it. This is where I have I'm showing your bluff and I'm gonna fucking call
I want to ruin this is bitch is life now
You have no idea I have something else
Here's your that's not our name. Let me Katrina. It's another name of some other woman something else playing for her
That's not a real name Christina
Yeah, yeah, she's right and and she might get her license stripped
Christine shut the fuck up
Sorry, sorry guys go ahead
I'm sorry, you guys go ahead, I'm sorry.
Christine, quiet, quiet, quiet, lady.
I mean, she's 85 years old singing I Want Candy,
Aaron Carter's song.
Oh my God.
Really, really, Christine, stop it, stop it.
Jamie, I'm so sorry. Jamie. I'm sorry to you
Jamie, I'm sorry. I mean, I just want them to leave
Hey, no, I don't want Christine. Christine. I want to go bridge jumping with you and I'm gonna cut your I'm gonna cut your line
Yeah, we're gonna go jump in the water like you said, but I'm gonna cut your your budgie cork
I'm gonna walk. Oh my god. Don't cut it. Don't cut it so you don't cut it
I mean
You gotta
You be exposed expose
You're fake christine. You're not the steven king car. Okay
You're not your liar
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
I'll be right back guys. I'll be right back. I've talked to somebody probably she's in Florida. I know exactly
I have people in Florida where she's that she does not need a fucking take care of anybody or have her license
Or she needs to be ripped that license
Yep, she's threatened a freaking trying to kill me
You're gonna call the board on her crystal call the board
But I'm gonna have a doctor called the board on her in her state
Yeah, I got something planned really great
And we're gonna send all the fucking videos
Because I got I have a lawyer guy that clips these fucking weird shit
I don't want to tell you guys, it's just because I am like, you know, a military family.
I understand.
Crystal, what you think about Bita, you and Bita cool now or how's the situation with
Bita?
No, she's gone.
Oh my God.
She's going to go back to her country shortly.
I mean.
No, we'll be working on that too.
We're gonna get that witch back into her own country.
She doesn't even believe in fucking,
godly fucking our own religion.
Like, at least we have to have one thing going on, okay?
You don't have to be religious,
but you have to breathe in some kind of religious ways.
You know like a good and evil are you know evil is bad
You know what? I mean like that and she doesn't believe that so we have to kick these
Horses out of our country
Victoria's over here trying to defend beta. She's American. She said she's not American
I'm a hundred percent American.
No, not you. Be there.
Victoria get on the panel girl. She's not American. So Victoria come up
I want to hear you defend Bita and I want to hear your sweet voice
Victoria get up get the fuck up here. Bita's American
She's born in Michigan
She was born in Michigan she's American she was never born in Michigan. That's all she went in there wrong
Yeah, is she is she a little
She wasn't even born Iran. She was born Iraq show her
Crystal I mean, has everyone seen this picture. I know I don't know. That's what fucking crazy fucking
Crazy eyes is saying. Oh
Andra mayors. Yeah, she's crazy. Yeah. Have you seen this picture? Look at this
You see this one crystal look at this
Oh, yeah, you saw that one. Mm-hmm. It's either one with Tommy James
Why just come on
Why now but look at this one crystals you like this one crystal this one
Alex has a crazy imagination dude. Crystal you like that one. Oh
Yeah
It doesn't look like her but
I met her in person it does look like her. No, it doesn't
Crystal don't contradict me lady. Okay. No, I'm answering the cat. It's okay
Yeah, and it's okay
You guys see this one is sweet it's okay. I love you sweetheart. You see this one is Jamie you thought of the sweepy
What
Let's sweep your AVRC sweepy in person
No, yeah, uh, Sweet Pea
I'm a how you know she that big
You don't know I know
And you can hear it in her voice dude, don't even lie
She snore as she saw
that's what she looks like, okay?
but she has a beautiful voice, that's what all fat people do
that's her, that's her!
I don't know if you know, fat people have the most beautiful voices
I caught her I caught her. Yes. I am a beautiful voice. She does but so does phone sex operators that are 500 pounds, right?
Yeah, I know that's not get it wrong. Let's not
disrespect her voice. I don't I mean so does like 600 pound people
They have nice voices. That's why they're phone sex operators, but if you look at them, they're 600 pounds, right?
I bet if sweet pea turned her camera on every one of you females that are up here running your goddamn mouse right now
That's what I said
Cam up work. What'd you say? I can't hear you fight. Can you hear me? I can hear you sweetheart. Yes
War dog. I guess you know maybe we're talking sweet accidentally dropped off my panel. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
that
We hear you Jamie
No, I just want to make sure because I almost dropped down again. I love you Jamie. I love you too, Jamie
And I love Jamie. I can't hear psych. You can't hear me. You can't hear me
Hello, Kissy. You know me. I
Think cuz you dropped uh, you dropped war dog it messes with her. Yeah, it does it does something
Okay
Yeah
Okay, you said you are Jamie. Yes, I am. Yeah. Yeah
You're insulting me again
Say you bitch say to my face you bitch
You never did you never did Jamie on that clip. I wasn't talking about that Katie
I was talking about a different Katie by the way. I was talking about this Katie that was involved with
the fucking
psyche is your name
remember
you're fine
it wasn't that katie
i already said
i was like thinking that he was talking about that
katie because that's the only katie i've actually
and i don't even know
the other katie because i haven't
talked to her
ever but she's been
like super weird
to me
I was the one that was like more vocal.
I was the only one being vocal.
It happened everywhere else.
I was just the one vocal-ing it.
Just saying.
Can you hear me now?
Yeah, we hear you.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, you're good.
but I got a lot of shit for that that other Katie for the chop shit and that
that lady is like child I don't even know how old she is because she didn't
say how she was and she wouldn't show her face or anything but back in the day
they said that she was underage and that's why she got kicked from everybody
You know
She wasn't around for a long ass time for years
Crystal is it true that Christine? What was the question? Is it true that Christine is selling medication?
Is it true that you got fired for stealing medication or work is that true? No
My god, she got fired for stealing meds. I know something was
Everyone's saying it's too. Really true
Man, is it a question? That was a question, but I think that's where this person say it's gonna be true and Christmas
That is true
Christmas that is true, too. I
Have no idea if it's
I don't know
Listen, I know people that are in the field, the nursing field, and these people will get
into drug activity, or they want to, I don't want to mention any names, but they get into
So guys if you give me a like in the chat, you know, I do have 49 real viewers
It's a what I'm saying and there's a really a lot of amazing nurses like Tracy
Tracy may Tracy's a good nurse, but Tracy's just like spunky, you know spunky
She's a nurse too
She asked me an amazing nurse
Hey, I just missed talking to her. Yeah, Christine. Yeah, you know, I'm just saying these there is really great
Nurses out there
Guys you see them you want to see the most insulting thing they said this is what they said about me look at I'm making it with Tommy James
I mean, guys, this is sick.
Man, I do not see one.
Look at that.
Is that real?
Again.
Why do you even a gay man wants Tommy James?
Oh, my God.
Is that really your floor?
What the fuck?
Because that's supposed to be your apartment.
Hey, hey, hey.
Elzo, Elzo.
That's crazy.
I need help.
I need help, Elzo.
Can you donate two cups?
Shake my head.
But listen.
In your head.
I'll do 50 for an eyebrow.
If you for half an eyebrow Alex when I first night
Also send me a hundred dollars night. I'll save up an eyebrow
Boy, okay
What are you gonna paint them on?
You gonna paint them on afterwards?
What is your plan?
I don't know.
What eyebrow?
For $100.
Don't do it.
What did you think, Crystal?
$700.
How about half of your head for $70?
That's clumsy.
Half of my head for $250.
The whole head for $70.
$75.
Oh
Like we go figure it out
What are you for 250 tonight? Let's do it tonight for 250. I mean 250
Let me tell you when I first met Alex Alex. You got to talk to your man
me because
She really has long hair is a signature Jamie his long hair is a signature
By good times and by other people. Oh my god
I did not spiritually traffic anybody good times and that hey
I'll set up a half an eyebrow and half my head for 250 elbow do it
Like I'm trying to tell you it's not worth it, man. That's why I said the eyebrow the eyebrow go back
Look with a shank head. Have you seen my shank head?
I'll show you my shank head. Oh, thank you. How much for a half of your head shape?
Look how good I will look look at this. He wouldn't keep it though
Look, that's why you want your head seen like I look like I look like I look like William Shatner
I'm so I'm so I'm so cute. Oh you shave your head. Don't shave your head because you already won, dude.
I need something
Okay, we'll do it we'll do it it's like he awakens catch up or Venmo
You know that Eldo and then wanted me to kill myself.
Okay, what?
Oh, Crystal, come on, come on, come on.
And, uh, I won that.
The battle's already shaped.
Crystal, come on.
Let me apologize to me for it.
In Minecraft.
Yo, wasn't WarDog and J-Bro cool?
You know J-Bro black, right, WarDog?
Black?
Yeah.
Says we're all right and all this all this racist shit in the back
I'm saying sick about fell asleep. Yeah, he fell asleep. Look at that. Oh my god. Fuck
A dirty Mexican get that nigga out of here
Apologize out of here out of here. Say. Oh
I need to see you something let me say something. Oh, though. Let me say something. I'm gonna hear huh
Oh little crystal. Okay crystal. I see you girl
Yes, sir
Oh, no, what the hell's like what you doing? I'm shaking my booty for you
All right, come on. So you gonna make me uncomfortable. I'm out to get up. Come on. So I'm not saying man saying man
Say man the one that like watching
Every male creamer and has to intervene never let that
Oh my god, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Did I just do that on camera? Oh my god, I'm live
I thought we were in a private chat. I mean there's a private chat
We're private chatting
What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it
Be a hero. He's a man. It's $5. I mean come on
My money getting tight, you know, if you shave right now and get one of your eyebrows, I'm gonna send you 50
I don't play about money
Myself now
Can't say man can't show me anymore. I don't think unless he hasn't got the memo
Oh, you're striking I made you crystal striking. I'll be showing you fake
Say motherfucker, you're an n-word say get the fuck up bitch
Mexican get up now come on you disrespecting clumsy dog come on
Can you hear me? Yeah, I can't hear elbow
You can hear me? Hello?
Jamie.
Oh, Marcia, you're making fun of me for choking on my Big Mac.
You're going to hear me. What the hell?
Jamie
You know what I'll come right what just happened I can't hear although maybe it was the phone
No, when he uh, when he removes people and messes with your your body your thing. I don't know why it's weird. Oh
She can't hear me
Now I really can't hear it's with the microphone. I'm sorry. Yeah, that's it. Who's who's that shit doing too early somebody was having
Oh crystal crystal in there. That's crazy that
And here's that's crazy
It's been doing I think I think stream yard been on the update or some shit because when I leave that the stream yard
I'm still up here like I got that shit guys 89 viewers 89 viewers guys. Let's fucking go
They're here for crystal superstar. I know she's fucking hot as hell crystal
They might be waiting for you to shave that eyebrow, that's what they're waiting on
I'm not gonna rob you man
I'll shave off
I don't believe this
I don't want to do this
150 dollars half of my head
right now
Yeah, it is in style right now.
If you do shave up, just dye it blonde and then you'll be in style.
Oh, so what, how much, what if you just cut the middle of your hair?
The middle.
Under the middle of my hair, $200, I will shave right down the middle.
That's too much, man.
I ain't got too much.
We can help, anybody want to help with that?
$200, I'll shave half my head right now, through the middle.
like, like, like, like, like the guy from, uh, fucking Goonies.
What do you mean?
I'm telling you guys, 200, you guys, $200.
I'm getting tired of that.
Every time someone drops.
Oh, for funny.
Oh, you just want dough for funny.
I'll do it right now.
Guys, I'll save half.
I'll go right through the middle.
$200 tonight.
Although was it like $75?
I mean, how much would you do?
How you gonna up the money? Come on. I'll leave it for a week
I'll leave her. I'll go. I'll be like that for a week. It can't you can't grow it back. I mean, I get what you say
You ain't gonna cut the rest of it back and this person's midnight killing me and cat
Hey guys guys I
Can get weed I can get fucking like groceries and shit like that guys anybody want to help me out
it's okay if you don't want to I don't I can get a dollar like all for the whole
week I've been basically begging and putting myself in here for a week what
is that crystal crystal you want to help
That's cool. Okay. Never mind. Never mind guys. I'm gonna tell you it's early in the day
I'll give all my hair. I'll give all my hair
You're gonna get there just as early
I'm gonna leave. I'm gonna leave here you guys can hang up. I'll but I'll stop
Why do you want to get rid of your hair? Why does he want to look in?
Who got money in the chat man who got money all y'all want to be miles, but don't support psyche
Come on man. Y'all don't some shit man 2020. I know you I mean your name 20 give me my 20
I would not support a haircut. Yeah, who else in here? I'm gonna call all y'all miles out except Jamie Aaron. What's up, Aaron? Come on
Well, we gonna do it curse though. We got to get the money to go
Cutting his beautiful hair
In here like that, it's everybody the same I wrote one
About war dog for one fucking second
Yeah, war dog is saying racist shit in the back and he was friends with J bro. Like we're dog you
J bro is guess what
I was saying racist shit in the background.
Yeah, let me see.
Explain, yo, though.
So, don't trip.
What is don't trip, fuck, bigger?
What does that mean, buddy?
You think I typed that?
You guys want me?
Okay.
Okay, see you.
Oh my god.
Clumsy
This man is delusional. He's delusional as hell, bro. He said do you do you think I typed that with his fucking
Name is right
He's on a channel. What's up? These children Samuel's brother is Gabriel
He knows that he's not stupid. These people the whole summer and I'm not gonna
Charges or something is what I heard the oldest one though. I got to get a
We got he's right. He's right in racist shit in the bag. It's a black man. Like
To go back to jail
Is this guy about to go back to jail and gel
Does this guy really want to go back to gel just to go like crack a dog now he believe in aliens
What
Who called me daddy
Who told who said okay daddy come on don't be doing that to me
Am I here shit?
I'm a, I'm a just-
Crystal!
Yeah!
Hey, J-Bro!
Hey, J-Bro, you know that your charges
are about to be out because you just got out of prison
like fucking one month ago?
You don't think we know?
Ew!
It's actually like three months ago,
but it was right about things actually.
I think he didn't even tell us, but I know exactly.
But guess what happened after that?
Is that you fucked over yourself.
And you wanted to disrespect people that don't need it.
And you ruined everything about Sam-Anne
and now you are gonna go back to prison for it.
I'm not gonna lie. Shout out to Eldo because if it wasn't for Eldo like said man wouldn't have a apartment
You know I'm saying he has to pay that rent somehow. You know me
Tell you I'm telling you he can't pay shit. He act like he worked like bro. You don't work. You slow as hell
How what are you gonna be able to do?
What type of job can Sam and really fucking do what type of job can see a man do?
No, I'll give you a psyche laughs like you fucking
Some people row and I'm not gonna lie like that. That's yeah, you know, I mean your pop. It's a deep
Can you yeah, but I can't hear Eldo. Oh
We're good who just laughs
Stupid phone this is a new iPhone. I don't get this. No, it's not your phone. It's connection
Yeah, it doesn't have anything to do with your phone. It's just stream yards like he said, yeah
But listen
Crystal can you still hear me? Yeah. Oh, you sound beautiful. You have a beautiful voice
Jamie you have such a beautiful voice
Oh, she can hear me we're talking to each other
There's a way she can fix that though. I think she has to download
some shit
I think she has to download the stream yard app you guys can't hear so she's gonna have to come back. Yeah, it could site
Yeah, if she's on a regular web browser that she gonna keep happening she got to get the stream yard app
Yep
Yeah, cuz that's the only way my up. Oh, you got a iPhone or no
Not iPhone, but the fucking Android that I had bro it fucking made me fucking do that
update
Off a real year Android. I haven't had too much too much issues, but with the iPhone I heard you had to download the actual app
Yeah, maybe do like the what is it called the verification and all that shit like yeah
So crystal when we go like try to fix this with beta. I want you to try to make make amends with beta if possible
Dude, I don't I didn't want to be friends with her from the beginning dude
I mean, is it because of the Iran war to run USA war is that is that playing a role?
Sure, I'll make it all war. Okay
Yeah, you can make it that
Yeah, I fuck fuck them. I mean, oh, that's not that's not real
Yo
That's not true though, but I mean I'm just saying I'm willing
You know, like come on say why I saw you chat. I just noticed I can chat talk about goodbye
I'm out of here. Get your boy Jamie if you can hear me guys if you guys ever paid attention
Beedah's been doing that to me for years for years and years and years
She only shows up and she likes to sabotage stuff same with Jim Nick before so what so what she been doing?
Well, so what be the duty though? What are you talking about be specific?
Oh, she doesn't like a friend group once I have a friend group like somebody actually fucking likes him
But like chills with me. She ruins it every single time
It's been three years. It's been for like seven years or some shit
But that's okay, dude, I am not like these girls I don't care about that stuff
It's not like they think
I, I think they want the spotlight and now she's getting it so good for her.
She got it once before remember when trashes showed her pussy, you know, you know, when
I actually, that was actually, like my, I actually got to be honest with you, let me
is that I showed her ready my teeth and then Trasha showed her pussy and then
And then beat off fucked a couple guys at night on stream
the
Um, our dude to blogger to bliggory bliggie. Oh my god
That night and then she she got on stream you can look it up. You can actually look it up
It's documented. She got on stream after that, right and she started doing all these dances and the window and stuff and
You know and I was like dude, I don't know, you know, I ain't trying to fuck my friend, you know what?
I mean go have fun, but she like it's weird how like
Any day that is nice. I have a like a nice day. They just they just
Dude
They just like wanted everything ruined for me
I don't know what together that was when Trisha in beat our friends by the way
Can you can hear us now and everything? Yeah, I'm bigger all that stuff out later. I downloaded it
Oh
They were trying to get him to fuck with me.
I don't get it, nigga.
I don't get it.
We're gonna cook that up though. Early morning. How about you nigga?
That makes this dumb nigga. I'm gonna make sure you sleep. Make sure you sleep. I'm next. I ain't next. I got you. I ain't next. I got you.
I like that bitch. They quiet you
Why don't you walk outside? Thank you, psyche
Go ahead Jamie. Thank you psyche. Oh, yeah. Thank you psyche
Oh, you're another dude out of here to come on, man
These I'm gonna say nothing, bro
They remember petitive man. He keeps saying the same
Telling you
You telling you bro
These females be mind their business, bro, and he keeps on attacking them, bro
That's why I don't like about that nigga like leave the females that don't want shit to do with you, bro
Could understand if she's like attacking you or something, but she hasn't been doing a motherfucking thing to him, bro. I
don't
Literally you don't I know you don't Jamie. I fucking know you fucking don't
I'm your fucking simp. I don't give a motherfuck man. Like I fucking see it. It was fucking weird
He likes attacking fucking famous fucking guys
No disrespect to psyche, but in females. That's who I'm friends with
Yeah
I mean, no, he thought he was coming back up. God. Yeah
It's great
Though bathroom bro waking up like that, it's crazy see if he would just have a simple conversation
He'd be alright, but he come up here yelling, you know, I mean just have a conversation
I'm not sure
Crystal you still there, baby
Yeah, and I'm none of that so I had to go pee
Yeah, wash my hands and now I'm thinking about how fucking irritated I am I
Should call
His own homies don't fuck with Sam and Sam and don't fuck with me
Man, I'm about to cause the fucking homies
No, I'm just reading chat. I don't know who Victoria's. I'm just saying hi on day homies
Vicky Vicky is uh, she Vicky not bad man. Vicky cool. I Vicky cool. That's really Vicky, you know, I really like Vicky
I think she's
brilliant honestly
Well, yeah, that's the first time I saw her like here. So I wanted to say hi
Oh, I didn't hear her here. I was in the I was in the bathroom right in here. Oh, no, no, no in the chat
Oh, I didn't see I didn't I was in yeah, I
Can't hear Eldo is it?
My phone history. Sorry, Jamie. I work to
I'm what oh, thank you
Oh my gosh, I love that. You're so positive and you fucking you really are a writer
Let's be a man back up man. Give me one more chance site. If you can't say give him a chance, man
Because people see a lot of bad things about
You know, uh
The situation with VP and she's had a weird situation and she's came above that and beyond and now she is like defending her and being like, and I love that.
That's great. That's great. You know, like, not that I agree with everything, but you know, it's like, it's good.
Yeah, and you know what? I don't think that anybody should be like
like if
Before I think that VP got me fucked up because like okay, I
Told and I was like, you know these things there's a movie about this actually I
Forget what it's called, but
It had Emma Stone in it. Oh
Stone, yeah
But it's about where she was like in college and she was like
She was like an internet person and then she was like
letting people say that they had sex with their
Her clout. Oh
Think I remember that that movie just
Anyways, I feel like I know you're talking. I felt like that like I've unconnected when I see that movie
Yeah, man, you want to come on?
Easy a I think
Say man, you want to come back up? I can't hear sight. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah
Like we are like all easy a's around here. You know what I mean? Like
Yeah, it's easy a that's what it's called. Yeah
I want to say it say man, I'm about to say it all right now. We'll just give it a minute
Give it a minute. Are you clumsy are you talking about? Can you hear psych at all? I can't help I can't hear L. Doe either
Yeah, I can hear psyche. I can't I can't hear me Mike check my
Let him up. Let him up. Let him up. Let him up
50 bucks. Oh
Yeah, fucking pay up, buddy. Yeah, he made a $200 on me to give me off his show
Yeah, fuck him
I
Okay, if it starts striking him if he doesn't give you money for the fucking show he doesn't even do no commentary
He only knows fucking 12 words
He knows
I
You know what I'll just stay in the chat, but maybe I'll come back up. I'm trying to figure out how I can't hear psych or Elton
Tell her did not because somebody tell her she got a download that a stream or that
She she did Jamie a recent if you
Okay, all right
Just come on and come back
I'll reset the phone and then you want me to get kicked first or dry leave. What do I do? No, you stay. I want you to just leave
Okay, I'll be back. I'm right back up and then just close it out. Just close everything out on your phone
Or whatever you're on
And then come back or maybe that's what I did
Closed everything out. She downloaded the app now and
Usually when you do stuff like that you have to like restart your phone sometimes just to make sure everything works
You know like updates and shit
But for her to be able to hear that makes sense she can hear us but she couldn't hear but I couldn't hear you guys either
Remember it was like weird. Yeah, that's what psyche was saying. Yeah
The same is still backstage. Yep
Come on cycle about for at least two minutes, man. Two minutes, man
No, he's gone he's gone. Oh my god
Oh, shit. Sorry.
Hello, you don't want to donate for my life.
Yeah, but that's what I was saying just two minutes.
It wasn't the whole time.
No, you know what?
You should at least give you ten dollars.
No, no, no, no, no one's not one dollar.
No, he needs ten dollars to speak to me.
Yeah, no one's donated one dollar, not one dollar.
He's not going to speak to me unless you he donates ten dollars to you.
Okay
I will not speak to him and I will only okay, which elbow
Hello damn what it wouldn't nigga, what it y'all think it's me, huh?
Bo you be timing people out and getting people water breaks over the smallest things that man shut the fuck up, bro
How about my ass?
Shut up, nigga.
You're a psych dick.
Three.
Hey.
Two.
Psych get more.
You're gone.
This is mad.
You're done.
You're done, son.
I
Go get another fucking spike of fucking wrong
Sorry, you need money
Yeah
Sam and you were begging Nana for a happy meal
You banned them because you didn't want to send you fucking five dollars for a happy meal. You remember that
Oh, no, no
She's not calling you Sam and she holds me not you
True like the bitch he is psyche
Yep
He's still my shit he has nothing original
He says passionate because I did he says baby. He's like, oh
Like like he stills all my fucking shit. I can't even say no more
You know that controllers are doing that and I had to stop doing shit that I was doing because I hate her
Like that's a good person Maria. Didn't you say that Sam and was acting like a weirdo like
Like he wanted you like
No, I never he was not controlling his fuck like he owned me. Oh
Okay control
No, but he was he was trying to act like he liked me like and that was not you know
I was not even like that
But he was trying to act like oh like me and then he was like
Yeah, you so gross. It was so sick
It was like so sick because he was like the fucking homie dude and I really respected him and then he started doing so dirty, dude
Hello
They put it you know what he started doing
What he started doing try to put it he started doing a slide little comments and doing little things and
Then making little jokey jokeys with his little
Discord friends because he knew I wasn't in discord and then he started making these big hole fights that I wasn't even a part of and then
Like I would have to deal with like being in the middle of this whole fight
And I wasn't even a fucking part out dude, you know what I mean?
Because I'm like a protective person. He took advantage of my sweet soul
Okay, how's that? That's what he did. Can you hear us? Yep
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Being disrespectful to me in the DMs and his
Nono
Came out of the woodworks right and she came out just to tell me that she she cried to me
Said she she felt so sad for me
What if I ever done though, I just gonna call you
She said
She said she felt so not to you Jamie not no not you Jamie. Oh, okay
No, no, not you nothing to do with you Jamie. I
Just wanted to ask him what I did. He can't even answer. I can't answer
Hello, I'm getting put backstage
Backstage talking exactly what the fuck I came
You but in
Who Katie talk shit about me talk shit, and you'll be jacking it you'll be tick
Katie be
What in here
Because he don't share the bullshit I hear
What what I
Beed up be doxing to what are you talking about?
No, no, I'm talking to me. Listen, it was actually Easter last year, dude. It was
Easter last year, dude. It was Easter last year, dude.
Exactly, not an extra choir, right? They don't want to cut that art.
Maybe it's got some people cash out, people roll numbers and all that.
Oh, that's one doctor cash out. That means they can donate money to them. Come again.
No, she adds people in group chats random people. She had a deal. Oh my god. Oh, you didn't know that you don't know that story
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh
But what did I do?
He's trying to make up something else. He's trying to change a subject
Do you see how he's trying to deflect and project on other shit? Yeah
Yeah.
Pay up, Samman.
Pay up.
No, listen, what he did was really shady,
and he was being very mean to me.
And he was doing stuff in the Discord,
because I didn't have a Discord.
So he was making bad pictures, and Nono showed me the shit.
And it was like so crazy, and he was like, that's when he became friends with, uh,
Bita, and Bita did not like me. You don't even know.
And I only became nice to Bita because she was getting so bullied.
And I never liked her. I just felt sorry for her.
And then I like to you know, it's not like I hate anybody or anything. I kind of like everybody, but
It's I mean, I like I mean, I like things about her and stuff, but I
Don't know
It was like a weird thing at that time and then and then
But you don't even understand is that I knew what they were doing
And I knew what you were doing and you were part of it clumsy and I knew what everybody was doing
They were like and then that's when
they were coming at me strong dude even fucking control I mean they want to
mean yeah you're gonna believe what you want but what I'm gonna be as Rose I
can't with you I never dug that deep into your fucking life before you did
though I was like one of the first people you try to fuck with and you
No, you got upset.
Yeah, yeah, you fucked around and found out.
Yes, you fucking did.
And that's when you started fucking around.
So what did I find out though?
Because you've got a lot of people on your ass
Start hating you remember fucking Jesus. It was like one a day. She started fucking calling you out and then
But you start fucking with me and she called you out and you became a target dude
Like whatever how many fucking viewers she had? Yeah, you were a bitch at that time
Oh my god, so Gucci's called me out a hundred percent
A lot of people wanted to fuck you over
Even even your boy did thank you
I don't even know how many boy your prison I think fuck you over Aldi, right?
You gotta say because my boys all
That's why he
Crystal Marie you cannot be mad at Aldi because he didn't want nothing to do with you. Oh
My gosh, she was harassing me. Haven't you see and how
Stop
Weird shit to me you're weird. Oh to you guys are weird dude. I'm weird. I'm weird
You guys need to figure out life
Before it catches. Oh, I mean it's gonna catch
Okay, because that was just a little fucking that was just a little dare I had
Okay
There was just a little bear
Nigga that make me doxing kids old types of shit nigga
Yeah, nigga you want to tackage you wrote that in the DM to be there why niggas don't talk about that
Aren't you color cops? Nigga? I don't need a color cause you the weirdo nigga. Go ahead. Let's go cook it up
So Jamie what you want so Jamie so Jamie fun has the answer right Jamie you want to dance her back in a female when she
Jamie I'm talking to you. I don't use a female clumsy. I didn't know you a trimo. I know you. I know you take it up
You're a fucking stalker boy. You attack me. There's two
three miles up here bro. I'm sorry, Jimmy, but I hate this guy's guts.
What's one?
Lumsie.
For life. I hate him for life. He did he did weird shit to me before and I'm not
Ever gonna be cool with that guy. I just don't pick. Hang on a second. I can't get this stupid Android to shut up
I'm gonna say with iPhone. I just don't pick sides. That's you know, I get him. Yeah. Yeah, yeah
and I'm trying to be cool with clumsy
as much as I can be and I still
Fuck any of your fucking
I don't even know what I did to that and now it just made everything you just
drew everything back up, dude
And you make me
You're so sick and I fucking want to fucking rip your fucking head off, dude
Like, I can't stand this fucking guy, dude.
I can't stand my fucking son.
Damn, the chat cookin', chat to the chat.
Chat cookin', dang.
Clumsy shit, they're nasty as shit.
Facts.
They can try to play innocent.
Like, he's not nasty.
Pack yourself up, nigga.
You're the weirdo.
Big weirdo.
So are you fucking, you're fucking,
want to fucking be an owner of fucking humans.
They got into a meat bond.
Ha ha ha.
So are you say man? I can try to own me and shit. Mm-hmm. Oh
Try to own you now
He's trying to own
Trying to own me
Like he owns me like I'm haze. Oh
Is that what it was okay, okay? I
Don't even know what he is what?
I don't even understand what the beef is. Yeah, I can't I can't cook it up
Many people in line about it just like she showed be this ex-boyfriend people do
Talk about you don't need to talk. It's like you're Jamie or Katie Dan country mind your business
Are you talking about your work Christine?
That's gonna get every license fucking lift
How is that from her record?
How is that my my my what I've done how yeah, that bitch is gonna lose every license in the world
We're gonna make sure that shit. I will not bring her name up
He can ask me, but I I have more respect for her than that. So oh
Wow, you're so sweet, aren't you?
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Yeah, I'm just okay. I just want to know why
He came at me when it's not me that did it well that lady tried and I have it on record that she was saying that
I am the southern lady that was trying to say I think she wanted
You know what I'm trying to say that they were gonna get me
51 50 because they had a license in their area and that I made beat a mad
You know, it was crazy, but it's all in video and it was sent in and it's to license places to both Missouri and to Florida is what she said.
And her name is whatever.
Come back up here and have a conversation with you. I'll mute myself.
But you know, but that's what she wanted to play a game. She wants to play a game, right.
Are you coming up here now or we had a rap battle one time with Amanda. She's not here
tonight, but she's great. And Amanda is so awesome. Isn't she cool? She is so cool.
And she's so smart, dude. Very funny and smart. I love you both, dude. You guys are so great.
Why not just great humans like real great humans?
You can tell real great
I didn't get any of that
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Hey, I won't talk about her here at all. Yeah, I know
She's not here to defend herself and I don't know no bring her up and stuff. I got my other stuff
You guys want to hear him you can donate money if you want to hear Sam man if I got a catch up. No, is anybody
you should donate
Seven dollars to be on stream for seven minutes. Yeah
Seven dollars seven minutes. I'll let them up for seven minutes. And we're not even together anymore to get this stuff at but
Stupid I'm sorry. Um, you know, I really don't I was being
I'm trying to be cordial. I just I'm just trying to be cordial. I don't know
You know clumsy's done some fucked-up shit, but you know, I'm just trying to be cool
And I fucking hate the dude. He's like one of the people I hate
It doesn't matter anymore
Why do you want bringing it up then it doesn't matter now it's what happened five years ago in
Five years ago now. Well, I don't know it was probably like about let's I mean ask somebody
It's probably five years ago that you how long you've been harassing me for about five years. I am
Okay, yes
So whatever whatever
You fucking call it what you want. You've been a bitch to me for five motherfucking years now, and you've been trying to fuck with me
I'm gonna let you talk shit
Why cuz I don't simp for you. I'm not like that
I am not simping they're not simping for me. You fucking retard
I mean, I said for each other to try to get girls to like I'm so sorry that you don't understand that these guys
Don't simp for me either as much as fucking same and does that mean same man had this weird
So salmon was simping over you
He never sent for me. Me and Sammy were like, homies.
And never, no, we never, no, no, no, no. We were just friends, dude.
Okay, well, we're about to say that.
But he started being weird.
Like he started saying that I couldn't go anywhere and like go on this and like
Saying like I couldn't go on this podcast or like I shouldn't go here like I'm doing this and like I was like
Go fuck yourself. I'm a fucking grown-ass bitch
I'm gonna go wherever you want. Exactly
And then we like
And then well, you know what he started doing then after that he started doing that and then he said oh
Somebody's donating and you know who's so funny that night is that I put in I have like two
Masks and like a fate or like a lip mask and then a lip gloss and I put that lip mask on
And it's like white and like, you know, like thick,
but the other one is the same.
It's, it's like the same and he, and I said it
and he took a picture and it, and it,
cause it dried and I was like, oh, I'm going to do.
Right.
Oops.
Crystal.
Or I think your phone might have died. Oh
shoot
So it's different this where you told me to upload that at it's different now
I had to do that on my laptop because there was like a big update not the one recently
But like I think it was like maybe like a month and a half ago
There's a big update and they made me like
verify my book everything I had to sit there and literally show my ID oh wow
okay yeah and I was like what the hell and yeah cuz I was having problems too
that there was sometimes people couldn't hear me yeah yeah I had to do that
because it kept kicking me off I don't know why it even does that like with
What the iPhone though, like I know that's like top of the line. You know what I mean?
Probably it was too yeah, I
Just had an update to like put that
Stream yard like on there you said. Oh, you just gotta update is now
Uh, yeah, you told me the down you told me to load that app up on stream yard. Is that
What it was. Yeah, I'm not very coordinated when it comes to computers and shit. No, you're good. You're good. Yeah
No, it's yeah, as long as you had downloaded the app it might run a little smoother
But from what it seems like it might it might just be like a stream yard steam too
Yeah, it's really different setup this way the other way was totally easier, but
I'm learning
Exactly. Well, when you were when you were first coming on the panel, were you entering like through?
Oh, no, but like do you have an app for like?
YouTube and all that already. Yeah. Oh, so you went to the app then. Yeah, I think that's what was happening on one site kept
Dropping people off or when he left I couldn't hear
Yeah, that's that's weird, but it doesn't matter because when crystal left it didn't kick me off
You know like you said just yeah
Yeah, cuz you said that there was time you couldn't hear Eldon and there was time you couldn't hear Eldon
Yeah
Crystal you should have the phone like on my computer like I have my phone and then I'm like it
Like on my laptop so it never dies, right? So yeah
little setup right there Crystal hurry up psyche where'd you go bro I don't know
we're cycling but I'm not going to answer somebody that's not here and I'm
friends with her so that's off-limits
what she does is on her own I don't take sides so
That's the best thing to do around here. You know, it sucks you get judged for it, but I'd rather be judged for
I don't care what happens. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's just yeah
Here I knew this was gonna come with it. I don't even fucking have fun
No, like I'm not a lie like there's times I have fun on here. Like don't get me wrong. I do
You know, I mean, I wouldn't be coming back around if it wasn't like, you know, I knew this was gonna happen and that's okay
Because she's worth it. So
Hey, okay
Well, shut up to you, you know the meme because
on some real shit like I don't even understand why like
He was even coming at you like that like I
You you already know like I'll sit there and talk my shit, but you never
It's fucking stupid fucking stalker
Give me a sec. I'm gonna use the restroom real quick. No problem. Thank you. Bring your fucking ass back, bro
Stop flicking your fucking being
And thing wanted, I think they wanted crystal with the alien pose, Ness Hilaria's.
Oh, Raging, come on hurry up.
Know thing that would've been neat, huh? She got like the dinosaur down, but I'm not sure
Raging I don't know how to post that I think it's like it's posted if you scroll up
Think he has it posted. I
Think it's posted when you scroll up charisma has it posted
Yeah, no, I don't know.
Think, do you know how to post the link because I don't know on the phone how to do it here?
The phone, it rocks.
Thank you, 2020.
Okay, thanks. Thank you. Maybe that'll work.
Okay, thank you.
I know Ivana, that's for football days.
Nothing yet with Psyche.
Nothing yet, and Demon said that's not the right...
I don't know how to do it on the phone from up here.
Oh hell no, I can't turn this phone out shut up. All right. They need to be thrown in the ocean
I'm an iPhone person
Trying to connect my headphones real quick. I
had a friend that's very smart and because
What happened?
I only know iPhone at the bottom where the button's at because I was before the X, you know
What I'm talking about so I'm used to it
and then I don't know why didn't go to the Apple store or whatever because I
Went to Best Buy and got this huge phone, but it was an Android, right? And I'm like, what am I doing?
but my friend
Put the Apple settings on it, but it's
Not like an iPhone, but the minute I got the newest iPhone with the button that you know the the last model with a button at the bottom
It would take me where I needed to go because my brain was
wired that way because of
How I used to have it does that make sense anything new I won't understand unless you tell me
Yeah, no, no, I got you so pretty much him doing the settings on the Android kind of life
I gave it to my mom. No, it's just too much. So if it was an apple
I'm so used to the button at the bottom, you know, Lily made a couple of times, you know
And then I can scroll better
But when they did like how you can type at the top and then like at the bottom it was all confusing
Just my brain doesn't understand that so it's not registering
But I got used to it now a little bit, you know, so I can maneuver around
But the button has to be there if there's no button on one of these phones. I don't know how to use them
I'm just I got I got you. Yeah, Katie always tells me you have to rewire your brain. So I'm trying
Not in the way the way I look at it too like I have an iPhone and everything but I
Prefer and I enjoy this to me. It's more but you're used to it
Exactly, I mean, but I have dissociation. So when all those
Like apps dance around my brain doesn't understand. I can't collect it fast enough. Does that make sense?
It's just a I think it's just a trauma thing I'm
trying to relearn
Yeah, and you know once you
You'll you'll get there, you know what I mean?
But you know what you're comfortable with and at least you know, you know, you have some kind of
Way to be able to make it easier for you. You know what I mean? Yeah, uh-huh. Yeah. Yeah
And sometimes I just you know when you want to drag an app over from
Because I have so many apps on here that I want to get like one app over to the front or whatever
Mm-hmm. It starts going way too. I'm like, okay
I panic a little bit because I'm dissociated so I can't have that all at one time
Yeah, have you ever like try to like put it like, you know, oh god, that's what she said. Yeah, I can't. No, no
Yeah, you know why because it's
It'll be like different for me. I have to have everything the same
Let's say okay. Yeah, I'll be confused. I'll be confused. Yeah, no, and then that's understandable though
You know what I mean? You got to be comfortable with you what you know what you're comfortable with
You know what I mean? And yeah, so I lost memory. Yeah, you did that hit and
Had to relearn words over again that I thought that I knew but I'm sounding them out
though, you know
Uh doing the best I can
Well, I'm gonna be honest with you. I mean take it or you know what you want
But ever since I've been talking to you, I've never seen any I even know anything like that into kind of like, you know
Explained it. You know what I mean, but uh, I wouldn't have been able to even tell and that's just me being real
it's
would she say something global in Asia is what I suffered from so I only get bits and pieces of
memories yeah yeah but but 80s and 90s you know how I like my old school oh of course certain areas
certain certain things I could remember yeah like
Did I already say that already because no no no no no no no no that's what goes on in my house every day
It's like did I already sleep? I don't know because it's two hours too long or have I been up for three days?
I'm not sure because of the concussion protocol still. So it's like
It's all new
I've always wondered, you know, cuz I it's kind of my fault, but when I was away
I kind of caught a I guess a concussion. I would more or less say but I never got looked
But I never seen a doctor for it. I never went to medical for nothing and
For like a good I think
Three months I
dealt with like some crazy things that I could kind of like I wouldn't say I could relate the same thing you are
Saying but there was things that I knew that was all
Right, but it had to do with the certain situation. You know what I mean? I hit my head pretty damn hard and
Yeah, it was it was kind of tripped out because I didn't remember my name for like a good
It felt like it was only like in a couple of minutes
Yeah, like the hours passed and I was like what the hell and
Like I explain that to my bunk. Well the guy I was
You know chilling with whatever and he kind of explains like that sounds like a concussion
Yeah, like I have to realize like have I done that already, you know, because I don't remember if I've done it already
Yeah, then a wreck, you know, I have days like that like, huh, okay
And I think that's this, you know, well, I'm not gonna say normal for like, you know
Certain people at certain ages, but you know people deal with that as they get older
But you know from what you went through. That's yeah
creating
exactly
Well, I mean all you can do is take it one day at a time and
You know from what I see you're doing you're doing wonderful. You know what I mean? So I have a great teacher
Yeah, well, whatever you're doing just keep on doing it and he wants to pick on you. I'll let her let him
Yeah, I think I think psyche might have passed out
Yeah, and not to mention, you know like
Was that punctured punctured lung? No, you don't know what's it called? You have a bruised bruise
of bruised lung and bruised lung and sternum and kidney from there the seatbelt
But hey, oh wow
I know I got lucky
But if it wasn't for that C bill, it probably would have been worse talking to you. And the only thing I wanted that was friends with Katie.
I said, whatever you're doing, just keep on doing it. You know what I mean? I write everything down. I have milk pads everywhere
I know it's crazy, but it helps me. Hey
If that's what that's what helps
Do it. Yeah, like
Shout out to you shout out to you for real
Yeah, and let that be a lesson like on some most you're like a lot of people in chem
I take this is little joke, but like there's times like
take my seat belt I wouldn't say super serious but I kind of make sure if I
know I'm about to like be on like I'm highway freeway I always buckle up I
should be buckled up all times you know you know what I'm not only lucky but
I didn't realize how much freedom I had having that vehicle and having a uber the last six seven months like however long it has been
has been such a headache and
such a disappointment because
They're expensive and plus it's hard to get around still
Because I live way out in the country, you know, so oh
Oh, yeah
But the truck's in my driveway from that night
Like one page is always helping me and stuff there's like things that are bits and pieces that need to be done and
like
the sheriff's are dirty and like the tow truck, but hey, I haven't stopped and
Coming for you so
Buckle up because I got all the evidence. I'm right. Yeah, I'm right
Yep
Well, I like this day. Did you know in California? You know sheriff no cop can have your phone
at all
without a warrant
No, I didn't I know that I did not know that and I was kind of out of it that night
I mean, I'm not gonna lie, but so you know what? I want them to explain to me why you had my phone the whole time
Well, I'm not the criminal that you know caused the wreck
Yeah, but you treated me like it cuz I got the footage. They didn't want to give it to me, but hmm. Oh
Wow
And they laughed and it's not funny because it's a life-changing event
so I
Mean, yeah fucking of course and if I mean it fucking cops are fucking sitting there trying to make a joke about that shit
Yeah, that's that's yeah
and some people in this world they depend not I'm not gonna say depend but you know they they
Well, I guess that's a yeah, they depend on you know law enforcement to protect them at all times
No, to be you know fair and I I know it's not all like that
No, it sure isn't
I'm not stopping
Sorry, it's sorry sorry people like that especially for people that don't do nothing like
You know what I mean? Like, okay, I can understand if you're doing something wrong or whatever the hell, but
Yeah, I know exactly what you're talking about. Yeah
I remember there was there was a time where I had a
Certain um older female with me, you know, I'm gonna say too much, but uh, I had got put over one time
And they were just fucking with me
And they were pretty much like harassing her because of what they did to me. Yeah, because of me. And even after the fact that, you know, she wasn't around with me, she got pulled over.
And they would like question her. Like, you know, this was years ago, you know what I mean? But it's just how some of these.
Cops operate it's it's fucking crazy. Yeah, I didn't think they're I bet you they didn't think that you know
I was gonna get the footage, but guess what all darkness comes to light and
I'm footage dude. Yeah, I'm right. I time-stamped everything so I'm like my own investigator
Damn right I'll descend it
Just make sure you know
Do everything that you're supposed to do and make these motherfuckers pay for you know
Absolutely, we're trying to make a joke about some bullshit like that. You know what I mean cuz I
Mean I
Don't want to say you know, you know, I mean, I don't want to say too much on here or whatever whatever
I know you could care less or an end but you know, it's just
You know, I feel about shit like that. Sorry, that's fucking people. Oh, yeah, I know
Yeah, I
Just want people to know that nobody's above the wall. Oh
Never that
Hell nah of the badge
Be a DGE. They're not
Yeah, and there's an you know, I'm not saying you're trying to be here like even though
I've been in you know certain things in my life and I had like a certain hatred for like law enforcement
I still kind of do whatever, but I know there's still certain
cops out there that are
decent
but
It's people like that that makes you double think about the whole law enforcement because
What makes you think that these good cops don't know what's going on and they see it, but they allow it to go
You know what I mean like these
Breasts underneath the rug. You know what I mean? It's
The fuck it's corrupt like you said, you know, I mean, I'm not gonna argue with that. It's fucking corrupt
Yep
psyche fell asleep on us. Yeah, I think so too. I was waiting for him to come back on.
It's like, what's your plan for today, Jamie? I wish it was football season or whatever you do. I already got my drink.
It's coming. Don't worry. He'll be here soon. He switched over to NFC. Oh
You know what? I'm just gonna get that shit
You know what I was gonna say something I want you to be disrespected. So what I'm gonna do I'm gonna fold it
I'm gonna put in the bag and I'm gonna put it in a box and I'm gonna put it in the attic. No, no, no keep it
Oh, I'm gonna keep it. I'm gonna keep it right there in the attic
You'll never get another quarterback.
No, you know, you know, it's crazy is that a buddy of mine, he's like a diehard Cowboys
fan.
Like anytime there's a game anywhere close to him, you don't care if it's like in the
next day he'll go.
You don't care.
The old school people and his dad was the same way and his dad
Did the same exact thing he did he's called these
Big old and get these signatures and jerseys and they have a matter of fact they have a
My mistake and I think it's a football
that came from one of the games.
Oh, nice.
And I think he got it signature by a couple of people.
And this was like around the time when
I think Romo had barely even joined.
Who was else around when Romo joined the Cowboys?
Blue D.
Are you trying to go over there?
Well, I'm not too much a little as you know, I'm not I'm not a Cowboys fan, but when uh
Romo first joined, you know, the
Cowboys who else was uh on the team also around that time for the chat
I don't know exactly, but uh, yeah, he had a bunch of signatures of all kinds of stuff, but there's a room that's dedicated to just
The cowboys in maybe I could get a hold of him. Maybe he could send me like a video or a picture not to show you it, but
it's the
collage of just
All kinds of just oh
Any any any cowboys band would fall in love with that room. Oh
it asked I
Told him he better hope he never lets me into his house cuz I'll burn that move a book down
I'm just like I'm just
No one day fucking asshole fucking sent me a shirt and he got it, you know done whatever and
remember that I
Think it was called fear or no fear
people used to put it like in
back of their vehicles or whatever it has like a I
Wouldn't say with kid, but it was a person that was like taking a piss
And usually like he's like
There's some kind of saying whatever. Anyways long story short
He was taking a piss. He was wearing a
Cowboys jersey and
He thought it was funny to sit there and put my bear's logo
On the surface where the piss was hitting as a fucking joke
So I told him better. I hope you never invite me into that room
And he's never inviting me ever since I think he really took that shit serious
Oh boy
I'm gonna go ahead and jump out cuz I'm gonna pass him out on this day. Yes, Jamie and have a blessed morning you too
He's out chat. Bye guys